Hi.
Hi. Hi, Ben.
Hi, we have
a little bathroom emergency.
Oh, yeah, go ahead.
Uh, but before we do,
uh, are any of Joey's special
romance magazines in there?
No, no.
Okay, all clear.
Thanks, Phoebe.
Yeah, it's Rachel...
but whatever.
Hey, listen, can you
do me a big favor?
The Dean's office called
and said there's
an urgent meeting.
Can you watch Ben for,
I don't know,
like, an hour?
Wh-What about Monica?
She isn't home.
So, it would just be me alone?
Well, Ben would be there.
No.
Huh, um...
What's the matter?
You know...
it's just, uh,
I've never done that before--
me and him, alone.
Rach, he's not an ex-con.
Okay, okay, okay.
What do I do with him?
I don't know--
just talk to him.
Entertain him.
Keep him alive.
Okay.
Okay, Ben, come here.
All right, I'm going
to leave you here
with Aunt Rachel
for about an hour.
Okay? You going to be okay?
Yeah, I think so.
I wasn't talking to you.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
What about the second minister
we met with?
I kind of liked him.
You mean the spitter?
Come on,
he wasn't that bad.
Easy for you to say.
You'd be wearing a veil.
What about the third guy?
You mean the guy that kept
staring at your chest?
Can you blame him?
Sorry, I just don't
like the idea of when
I'm saying, "I do"
he's thinking, "Yeah,
I'd do her, too."
Well, then we still
have a problem.
With what?
Well, we're trying
to find someone
to perform our wedding
and they're all either boring
or annoying
or, you know, can't stop
staring at the ladies.
Ooh, you should have
one of us do it.
Phoebe, we're getting
married married
not sixth-grade married.
No, no, it's-it's a real thing.
Anyone can get ordained
on the Internet
and perform, like,
weddings and stuff.
I call it.
What?
No, it was my idea.
Guys, thank you
very much
but neither of you
is marrying us.
Does "calling it"
not mean anything anymore?
We are going to have
a legitimate member
of the clergy,
and when I say
"legitimate,"
I mean gay and in
control of his saliva.
Ben, you know
when you were a baby
you and I used to
hang out all the time.
I was your daddy's
girlfriend.
But you're not anymore.
No, I'm not.
Because you guys
were on a break.
Hey, we were not on a--
Okay.
When's my daddy coming back?
52 minutes.
So, no brothers
or sisters, huh?
But you know,
I had two sisters
and we just tortured
each other.
Really, like how?
Well, you know,
we would, um...
we'd repeat everything
the other said
or, uh, we'd jump
out of closets
to scare each other
or switch the sugar
for the salt
so they put salt
on their cereal.
That's a good one.
( chuckles )
Yeah?
You like that one?
Yeah, you're funny.
I'm funny?
Oh, thank God.
Well, I got
a ton of these.
You take a quarter...
take a quarter and you
blacken the edge, right?
And then you say
to a person
"I bet you can't
roll this quarter
"from your forehead
to your chin
without it
leaving your face,"
and then when they do it,
they're left with
a big, black, pencil line
right down the center
of their face.
Can I do it to you?
Yeah, I'm funny, Ben,
but I'm not stupid, okay?
So, did you find anyone
to marry you guys yet?
No, but horny-for-Monica
minister called...
wanting to know
if we were still together.
We're never going
to find anybody.
Well, then,
let me do it.
Joe...
No, I've been thinking
about it.
I'm an actor, right?
So, I won't get nervous
in front of people.
I won't spit, and I won't stare
at Monica's breasts.
You know, everyone knows
I'm an ass man.
That is true.
Yeah, and the most
important thing is
it won't be some, like,
stranger up there
who barely knows you.
It'll be me.
And, I swear,
I'll do a really good job.
Plus, I love you guys, and it
would really mean a lot to me.
Might be kind of cool.
So, I can do it?
Yeah, you can do it.
All right!
Okay!
Whoo! All right!
Okay, okay, I got
to get started on my speech.
Wait a minute.
Internet ministers
can still have sex, right?
Yeah.
( knock on door )
Coming.
I have a bone
to pick with you.
Uh-oh.
Yes.
Ben learned
a little trick.
Oh yeah, did he pull
the old...
That's right
that's right.
Saran Wrap
on the toilet seat
so the pee
goes everywhere.
Oh, that.
Yeah, that.
You know
I hate practical jokes.
They're mean
and they're stupid
and I don't want
my son learning them.
Oh, come on...
Saran Wrap
on the toilet seat?
You don't think that's
just a little funny?
I was barefoot.
Oh.
( laughing )
Now, tell me,
The toilet thing is
the only thing
you taught him, right?
Yes.
Hey.
Say, "Hello,"
to Reverend Joey Tribbianni.
You did it.
You got ordained?
Yeah.
Just got off the Internet.
Man, there is a lot of porn
out there.
Our minister.
Hey, anyway, I started working
on what I'm going to say
for the ceremony,
you want to hear it?
Yeah!
Now, listen, this is
just a first draft, so...
"We are gathered here today
on this joyous occasion
"to celebrate the special love
that Monica
and Chandler share."
Huh?
"It is a love based on giving
and receiving
"as well as having
and sharing
"and the love that they give
and have is shared and received
"and through
this having
"and giving and sharing
and receiving...
"...we, too, can share...
"and love...and have...
and receive."
Should we call
the spitter?
( knocking at door )
Hey, Rachel.
Hi.
What a nice surprise.
What are you doing here?
Well, you know
I was just
in the neighborhood
and I passed by your building
and I thought to myself
"What's up with Carol...
and sweet little Ben?"
Oh, that's nice.
Come on in.
Okay.
I'll make some coffee
and we can chat.
I'd love that.
I would love that.
So, uh, so where is
sweet little Ben?
I would love to have a little--
( yells )
( yelps )
I found him!
Very funny.
Come here.
That is exactly why
I've come here
to talk to you, okay?
Rach, you want some sugar
in your coffee?
Yes, but...
Do I want sugar
in my coffee?
No, just some milk would
be good, Carol, thanks.
Okay, do you remember
all that stuff
I taught you yesterday?
Remember all that stuff
Don't do that.
Seriously--
your dad doesn't
like pranks.
Seriously, your dad
doesn't like pranks.
Oh, damn it.
No, don't, don't say that,
don't say that.
Damn it.
No, go back to repeating.
Oh, crap.
Oh...
Okay, you guys,
I got a little more written.
You ready?
Yeah, o-okay.
"When I think
of the love
"that these two givers
and receivers share,
"I cannot help but envy
the lifetime ahead
"of having
and loving
and giving and..."
And then I can't think
of a good word for right here.
How about "receiving"?
Yes.
See, Joe, not that
that's not great...
but one of the cool things
about having somebody we know
perform the ceremony
is that it can be about us.
You know, it can
be more personal.
You can tell stories about us.
Ooh! Ooh!
Uh... okay!
Maybe I'll talk about London
you know,
when you two hooked up,
only...
only I won't say,
"Hooked up."
I'll say,
"Began their
beautiful journey..."
There you go.
"...by doing it."
Joe...
Okay, all right.
Um, so, uh, so,
how did it happen?
Did your eyes meet
across the room
and then the next
thing you know
you're in the
bathtub together
and she's feeding
you strawberries?
Isn't that what happened
with you and the bridesmaid?
Yeah.
I call that "London style."
No, that is not what
happened with us.
Ooh, but maybe you should say
it is
because London-style
sounds nice.
Yeah.
Okay, uh...
Well, I was, um,
really sad that night
because this guy thought
that I was Ross's mom.
Ah.
And Chandler was...
he was really sweet
and he consoled me.
Well, we drank too much...
Yeah, baby.
And I was
a perfect gentleman
and I walked her
to her hotel room
and said, "Good night."
Oh.
But then later that night...
Yeah, baby.
( knocking at door )
Hey.
Cute PJ's.
You're really living it up
here in London, huh?
Well, I wasn't exactly
expecting company after...
9:15.
Is Joey here?
Well, the last time I saw him
he was heading out the door
with a bridesmaid
and a bucket of strawberries.
So, uh, you're not still upset
about what that guy
told you, are you?
Wouldn't you be?
Well, look,
It's been a really
emotional time, you know?
And you've had
a lot to drink
and you've just got
to let that go, okay?
I mean, you were
the most beautiful woman
in the room tonight.
Really?
Are you kidding?
You're the most
beautiful woman
in most rooms.
( moaning passionately )
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
what's going on?
You and I just made out.
You and I are making out?
Well, not anymore.
But we don't do that.
I know, I just thought
it'd be fun.
How drunk are you?
Drunk enough
that I know I want to do this.
Not so drunk
that you should feel guilty
about taking advantage.
That's the perfect amount.
You know what's weird?
What?
This doesn't feel weird.
I know.
You're a really good kisser.
Well, I have kissed
over four women.
You want to get
under the covers?
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Wow, you are really fast.
It bodes well for me
that speed impresses you.
We're going to
see each other naked.
Yep.
You want to do it
at the same time?
Count of three?
BOTH:
One, two, three.
Well, I think
it's safe to say
that our friendship
is effectively ruined.
Eh, we weren't
that close anyway.
Eh!
( door rattling )
Joey, Joey, Joey, it's Joey...
Hey.
Hey, Joe.
I was just watching a movie...
Oh, dude, I'm so sorry.
No, no.
Hey, no, no, no.
It's cool. It's cool.
I'll only be a second.
I'm still with my bridesmaid.
Where are
all those condoms you brought?
They're in my bag
over there.
Oh.
Uh, could you leave me one?
For just you?
Yeah.
All right,
there you go, buddy.
Go nuts.
That's what that was?
Can you imagine
if I hadn't left you
that last one?
You two might have
never gotten together.
Ooh, ooh-- can you imagine
if I had sent that hooker
up to the room
like I was going to?
It's like it was in the stars.
PHOEBE:
Oh, yeah, it was
totally meant to be.
Tell him who
you originally wanted
to hook up with
that night.
What?
Who did you originally
want to hook up with?
Okay, fine, but please,
don't be upset, okay?
I was really
depressed, okay?
And really drunk.
I just wanted something
stupid and meaningless.
I just wanted, just sex.
So, when I went
to your room that night
I was actually
looking for Joey.
Yeah, baby.
No, baby.
Oh, my God.
You came to the room
looking for Joey?
Were you ever planning
on telling me this?
No, because I didn't think
it was important.
It's not important?
If it wasn't
for a bridesmaid
you'd be marrying him,
not me.
No, do you know how
unbelievably glad I am
that Joey was not there
that night?
Hey!
I'm a man of the cloth,
but I still have feelings.
Look, there is no way
you're doing
this wedding now, okay?
What?!
That's not fair.
It's not my fault.
I was off with
my bridesmaid.
And who's to say
I would have even
said yes?
I mean, I would
have said yes.
Chandler, look,
you are making
way too big a deal
out of this.
Everything worked
out okay.
It's just weird, okay?
I don't want to be standing
there saying my vows
and then having the mental image
of you and Monica.
I need...
I don't know what I need.
I need a walk.
Wait, Chandler, come on.
It's not a big deal.
Well, it is to me.
You wanted to sleep
with Batman
and, instead,
you had to settle for Robin.
This is crazy.
I know.
Robin is so gay.
So, now, what
have we agreed?
No more pranks.
And what else?
That you and Daddy
were not on a break.
Very good.
Rachel.
What are you doing here?
I'm just visiting
my good friend Carol.
Your "good friend"?
Yeah.
What's her last name?
Carol...
Lesbian?
Nice.
And by the way, that...
that line down my face...
The line
that prompted a student
in my last class
of the day to say, uh
"Dude, don't you ever
wash your face?"
All right, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
Listen, I don't want you
teaching my son
that stuff anymore, okay?
Fine, fine, but
I'll have you know
that once I taught
him that stuff
he called me Fun Aunt Rachel
and I loved being
Fun Aunt Rachel.
I'm glad you guys
were bonding, but...
Look, he doesn't have
any brothers or sisters.
Somebody's going to have
to teach him this stuff.
And I haven't
taught him anything
that a normal six-year-old
doesn't know anyway.
BEN:
Crap!
I got to go.
JOEY:
Hey.
You want this scone?
It came from me,
but it would probably
rather sleep with you.
Come on, nothing
even happened.
I just... I don't want
you to be upset.
How can I not
be upset, okay?
I finally fall in love
with this fantastic woman
and it turns out that
she wanted you first.
Yeah, for like
a half an hour
one night.
Chandler, she wants you
for the rest of her life.
We look at you
and we see you together
and it just...
it fits, you know?
And you just know it's
going to last forever.
That's what you should say.
What?
When you're marrying us,
that's what you should say.
Really?
I can do it?
I'd love it
if you'd do it.
Hey.
But those are the words,
those exact words.
Well, I don't
remember exactly, but...
it's pretty much about
having and giving
and sharing
and receiving.
Hey.
So you guys
doing okay?
Yeah, we talked and
Monica made me see
that I overreacted
a little bit
and some things
in life are
more important.
Yeah, baby.
I'm really glad
you guys are okay
but I just keep
thinking what would
happen
if you two actually
had hooked up.
Honey, dinner's ready.
What's my little chef
got for me tonight?
Your favorite.
JOEY:
Ho, ho, ho.
Fried stuff with cheese.
Yep... and lots of it.
Thanks, sweetheart.
In you go.
In we go, in we go,
in we go, in we go.
Ah...
How you doing?
Hey.
Hey, I'm sorry to do
this to you again
but is there any way
you can look after Ben
for a little bit?
I've got this
meeting at school
and he-he asked for
his "Fun Aunt Rachel."
Aw, well, of course
I will watch him.
We have fun,
don't we, Ben?
ROSS:
Okay.
I'll see you
later, pal.
Okay.
( laughs )
Wait a minute.
Ben, I can't
do it.
You've got something
on your back.
What?
That's great.
That is great.
What did we just finish
talking about, Ben?
All right, that's it.
Come here...
You... No...
You are in big trouble,
young man.
No, wait...
Ben, come here.
I am not kidding.
You guys...
( Ross screaming )
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! Ross!